(dramatic orchestral music)
Life bloomed from roots in sacred ground.
A love was cradled safe and sound.
A dream was whispered through the rain.
And a
And a prayer rose from pain. In our hymns,
Cottolengo, you are grace. In
our  psalms, a light no night erases.
In our voices, your love still flows. God
gave us Cottolengo. Forever we
sing, "Deo Gratias." Cottolengo,
the name we call home.
A shelter when the thunder roars. A vase
where delicate
hearts are held. A dream that time could
never fold.
In our hymns, Cottolengo, you are grace.
In our  psalms, a light no night erases.
In our voices, your love still flows. God
gave us Cottolengo. Forever we
sing, "Deo Gratias."
We are the roses time can't fade. We are
the joy Cottolengo dreamt. We are the love
etched in
Cottolengo's heart. Through every tear,
joy, and whispered prayer,
we'll still remain roses of Cottolengo. In
our
hymns, Cottolengo, you are grace.
In our  psalms, a light no night erases.
In our voices, your love still flows. God
gave us Cottolengo. Forever we
sing, "Deo Gratias." Caritas
Christi urget nos. With
Cottolengo, Deo Gratias.
(dramatic orchestral music)